A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
"NETFLIX
オリジナルシリーズ"
（セミの声）
SHAVED ICE
（チリンチリン）
（ゲームの音）
（ゲーム）
YOU LOSE
ふぁー
あ 大野(おおの)
Ah, Ono!
My, this is rare.
あれれ 珍しいな
小キックだけで
ベガを倒すお前が
You beat Vega using light kicks alone,
but you're losing halfway through.
途中で
やられっちまうなんてよ
If throw moves keep hurting you,
Five, four, three…
mash the buttons and joystick
to break free!
（ゲーム）
Two, one…
うあああ！
Look!
見ろ
お前が本気出さないから
Poor old Dhalsim is all beaten up
because you're not playing seriously.
ダルシムがボコボコにされて
可哀想だぜ
なんかあったんか？
Did something happen?
まあ いいや
Oh, whatever.
もうすぐ夏休みが
終わっちまうし
I guess summer break's almost over
ナーバスな気持ちに
なっちまったんだろ
so you're getting a little nervous.
そういえば土井(どい)のやつに
By the way, didn't Doi invite you
to the botanical gardens?
お花園に行こうって
誘われたろ？
実は俺も誘われたんだけど
He actually asked me along, too.
お前どうすんの？
Are you going?
（セミの声）
ORIGINAL WORK BY RENSUKE OSHIKIRI
High Score Girl
ZIYA HARUO
SMOE
ZIYA
AKIRA
ZIIYA
New Stranger
（明るい音楽）
Round 3
（春雄(はるお)）
おーい
Hey!
待っておくれよー
Wait for me!
（土井）
グズは容赦なく置いていくぞ
No mercy for slowpokes!
- 皆待ってんだから
- はーはー
You've been holding everyone up!
ふ…こういう時の皆という
言葉 重くるしいぜ
Yikes... Saying "everyone" really stings!
相も変わらず
トロくてダサい男だな
Just as lame and dull as ever,
this boy...
But!
だがそれでいい！
That's just fine!
コイツら男どもが
ダサければダサいほど
The lamer and duller these
guys are...
俺のトレンディーな一面が
一層際立つってなもんだ
the cooler and more stylish I'll appear!
男女でこういう所に
来るのもいいね
Boobs!
（チャン）
大野さん
Oh, Ono...
二人でのデートのお誘いは
散々断られてきたが
You may have turned me down
for a one-on-one date...
皆で行くなら
恥ずかしくないだろ？
but there's nothing to be shy about
when it's a group!
（鬼塚(おにづか)）
ちんろー
Willy!
このめったに訪れない
チャンスの場で
I'll use this once-in-a-lifetime chance
なんとか僕の株を上げ
親密な関係に…
and elevate my standing with her
to an intimate relationship...
そして婚約者になってくれる
事を約束させないと！
And then, I'll make her promise
to be my lawfully wedded...
へえ！
（鳥のさえずり）
（女子）
大野さんが誘いに
乗るなんて珍しいね
This is rare, Ono accepting
an invitation.
あまり気乗りしない
感じだったのに
You never seemed into it before.
（土井）
そりゃ僕のプランに
心が躍ったからだろ
That's because her heart leapt
upon hearing my plan!
美しい花を慈しみ
心を豊かにする
Oh, how gazing at a beautiful flower
doth enrich the soul...
Isn't that so, Miss Ono?
そうだろう 大野さん？
あーあ
I accepted this invitation to avoid
all that summer-break homework...
夏休みの宿題がたまってる
現実からの逃避で
誘いに乗っちまったが
お花畑なんて見ても
面白くもなんともねぇ…
But there's just nothing fun
about looking at a bunch of flowers!
おい土井
Hey, Doi!
このお花畑は
遊園地と隣接してんだろ？
There's an amusement park next
to this flower garden, right?
そっちの方に行かねぇか？
Let's go there instead!
- 勝手なこと！
- ひゃ 行こう！
-You... don't just change the plan!
-Let's go!
- あ 大野さんまで…
- レッツゴーよ！
Vamos, vamos!
Ono...
高嶺の花を賛美する
最高の舞台なのに…
This was the stage for glorifying
my beautiful flower...
（パッ）
PARK MAP
There's only one thing
that makes my heart leap.
（春雄）
俺の心を躍らせる
存在がひとつ
ゲームコーナーの存在…
There's an arcade!
- 大野の奴 覇気がねぇな
- ほーい
Ono doesn't seem too thrilled.
ふふふ 遊園地か
An amusement park...
僕を心強く見せる舞台が
揃ってるじゃないか
The perfect stage
for showing off my bravery!
目をつぶって行けば
大丈夫さ！
Don't worry now, just close your eyes!
つり橋効果も狙える
絶叫マシーン！
These terror machines will work
as a suspension bridge!
Ｂまで行けるかもしれない
二人きりの空間！
The perfect space to aim for second base!
（効果音）
あわよくばＣも！
Or third, if I'm lucky!
大野さん
Ono, how about accompanying me
to the Mysterious Woods Adventure?
僕と一緒に不思議な
森の冒険はどうですか？
それとも
ミラーハウスはどうだい？
Or how about the House of Mirrors?
迷うことなく一発で出口まで
エスコートしてあげるよ
I'll be your escort until the end,
no wrong turns!
迷うのが面白れぇんだろ？
But isn't it fun taking a wrong turn?
お前は遊びの
楽しみ方を知らねぇな
You have no idea how to have fun!
む！
Wandering around lost
ドラクエ２の
クソ難しいダンジョンを
迷って迷ってようやく抜けて
ほこらに着いたあの快感
in a mega tough dungeon
in Dragon Quest II...
- 今でも忘れられねぇぜ
- あ！
That's a feeling I'll never forget!
- このゲーム脳！
- うわ
You blasted gamer!
You made her run away!
- お前が余計な事言うから！
- 髪にムースつけてる
This jerk even has mousse in his hair!
ねぇアレに男女二人ずつで
別れて乗りましょうよ
Hey! Let's split into boy-girl pairs
and ride that thing!
That'll spice things up!
盛り上がるに違いない
What a splendid idea, Miss Onizuka!
それはナイスな
アイデアだね 鬼塚さん
それじゃペアは
Now, for the pairs...
主催者の僕が
決めさせてもらうかな
I, your gracious host,
shall decide them!
- 殿方ー！
- ぐああ！
- へへ
- なんだお前は！
Good, sir!
僕は大野さんと
ペアを組むから
I'll be pairing with Ono
and please, everyone, enjoy
your time in the skies!
各自思う存分に
空中で楽しんでくれ
（春雄）いいから一回降りろ
（鬼塚）へへへ
All right, all right, just get off me!
困ったな
こんな事になるなら
This blows!
If I knew it'd happen, I would've
gone straight to the arcade...
ゲームコーナーに
さっさと行きゃよかったな
矢口(やぐち)くん 矢口くん
ゴンドラの中に入ったらさ
Hey, Yaguchi!
Once we're in the gondola,
チンチンに骨があるのか
確かめさせて
let me see if there's a bone
in your willy!
Wi--
ちっ！
何言ってんだよ！
What did you say?
骨があるわけねぇだろが
バカが！
Of course there's no bone!
Are you stupid?
この目で いや
I won't believe it till I've felt
for sure with my own hands!
この手で確かめないと
信じられないのよ
As if I'd let you!
やらせん！
やらせんぞ！
- ちくしょうめが！
- ちょっー
You total weirdo!
えっ 殿方！
Good, sir!
殿方ー！　殿方ー！
Wait, good, sir!
殿方ー！
（カサ）
ふ…
ここのゲームコーナーを
見てから
After I've taken a look
at this arcade
I'll head home and polish off
that homework.
家に帰って宿題でもするか…
しかし夏休み最後の
ゲーセンだと思うと
But still...
it's quite a shame to think this'll
be the last arcade of the summer.
せちがれぇ
（ガタン）
あー
典型的な遊園地の
ゲーセンって感じだぜ
Well, this feels just like
your bog-standard amusement park arcade.
ゲームの種類も
ちょっと古いのばかり
All the games are just a bit old
クレーンゲームの景品も
劣化したものばかりだな
and even the crane games are
falling apart.
まー何にせよ
Well, in any case
こういう所が
一番落ち着く所だよ
this kind of place makes me feel
the most comfortable.
あれ 大野？
Huh? Ono?
うははは
やっぱお前も耐えられなく
なって逃げて来ちまったか
Looks like you got sick of it all
and ran away, too!
やっぱ俺は
こういう所がお似合いだよ
I guess this place does suit us best,
after all.
ここなら人に合わせる
必要もねぇしな
No need to deal with other people
here now, right?
お
「ゴールデンアックス」か
Oh, Golden Axe?
敵の乗ってた
モンスターに乗れたり
You can do stuff like ride
enemy monster steeds...
It's a pretty intricately-made game.
なかなか芸が細かい逸品だ
で 大野は
「キャメルトライ」か
And you're playing Cameltry?
画面をぐるぐる回して
ゴールにボールを導くんだ
You spin the screen around
and guide the ball to the goal.
（ゲームの音）
- う…
- な？
See? This game will give you
motion sickness if you're not used to it.
慣れてないと酔っちまう
変なゲームだろ？
（歩く音）
お前 今日は
ムスーっとしてたけど
You've been pretty glum today.
なんで来たんだ？
So why did you come?
楽しくないなら最初から
来なきゃ良かったのに
If it's not fun for you, you shouldn't
be here in the first place.
ああー分かった分かった
Oh, got it!
Got things you don't
want to think about, right?
思い出したくねぇ
事があるんだな
You don't have to always make
that face...
いちいち儚げな
ツラすんなや もう
まぁ 俺も思い出したくねぇ
事もあるし
Well, I've also got things I don't
want to think about!
Like... homework and stuff!
So let's play!
宿題とかな 遊ぶか！
（ゲーム）
しょーりゅーけん！
（ボタンの音）
スト２は相変わらず
行列ができてるな
They're lining up for Street Fighter II,
as always...
一人用の筐体が
一台だけだし
And there's only
one single-player cabinet...
待ってるだけで
閉園しちまうな
This place'll be closed
before it's our turn.
（バシ）
おげっ！　うあっ
What?
- なんだよ？
- うん
ああ
「ダライアス２」な
Ah, Darius II?
こういうデケー筐体
We don't have these big cabinets
in the tiny arcades nearby.
近くの狭いゲーセンじゃ
置いてないもんな
前作の筐体はなんと
The first game had this mad cabinet
with three screens
横三画面の
凄まじいゲームだったが
今作では残念ながら
二画面筐体になっちまった
but sadly this second title
only has two.
それでもすごい迫力だろ？
But it's still pretty neat, right?
（チャリン）
二人同時プレイも
一層燃えあがるぜ
The co-op play can get
really exciting, too!
（ゲームの音）
（歩く音）
Well, neither of us is any good
at shooter games.
お互いシューティングは
得意じゃねぇからな…
うん？
今度は「スペースガン」か
Space Gun this time, huh?
映画「エイリアン２」
みたいな
It's basically a first-person shooter
based on the movie Aliens.
ガンシューティングって
言えば分かるかな
怖くてグロくて
It's so scary and gore-filled
you might pee yourself!
オシッコちびっちゃうかも
しんねぇぞ
- やりてぇのか？
- うん
Wanna give it a shot?
（ゲームの音）
後退だ
後退するぞ大野！
Retreat! We're pulling back, Ono!
足元のフットペダルを
踏む事で
By stepping on the foot pedal,
スクロールを
逆行させる事ができんだ
you can make the scrolling reverse!
Let's fight these aliens
from a distance!
エイリアンとの距離を
あけながら攻防戦だぜ
（銃の音）
おい お前…
ペダル踏みっぱなしだろ？
Hey, your foot's stuck on the pedal!
We can't play if we don't advance!
前進しないと
ゲームになんねぇから
（キイ…）
おい おい大野？
Come on, Ono!
Ono!
大野さん？
（大野）
はぁ…
けっこう来る物があったろ
It really does you in!
あのゲームをやった後
After playing that game,
the fear leaves you super tired.
恐怖のせいか
どっと疲れるんだ
じゃそろそろ
土井の所に戻ってやろうぜ
Well, we should get back
to Doi and the others soon.
あいつお前のために
この日を企画したんだから
That kid planned this day for you.
Can't help feeling a bit bad about it...
フビンで仕方ねぇよ
うん？　え
なに？
What?
（ゲーム）
テヤー！
FINAL FIGHT
- 「ファイナルファイト」？
- ふん
Final Fight?
Ouch! Are you sure?
いいのかよ
こんなんやってたらそれこそ
皆に置いてかれちまうよ
If we play this, everyone'll definitely
leave without us.
う…
大野さんはいずこへ？
Oh Ono, wherefore art thou?
（鬼塚）
えひひひ
観覧車で大野さんには
逃げられるし
She ran away at the Ferris wheel
こいつと二人で
乗るはめになり
so I had to ride with this weirdo...
チンチンに骨があるか
確かめられるし
and even had my thingy checked
for bones...
（鬼塚）
どっせい！
Tackle!
大野さんとＢ以上の
関係を望んだ罰か…
Is this punishment for hoping
to get to second base with Miss Ono?
（ゲーム）
デヤーッ！
（ボタンの音）
デヤーッ！デヤーッ！
「ファイナルファイト」は
地元でいくらでもできるのに
We could play Final Fight as much as
we wanted back home...
（ゲーム）
うおお！
ていうか 気合
入りまくってんな大野
But Ono, you're really getting into this!
デヤーッ！デヤーッ！
お嬢様の考えてる事が
まるで分からん
I've got no idea what goes on
inside this young lady's head.
（虫の音）
Look, Ono! It's already sundown.
見ろ 大野
空がオレンジ色になってるぜ
完全に置いて
行かれたっぽいな
Looks like we've been left behind.
お前は一機も死なずに
You just had to go and beat
Belger without dying...
ベルガー
倒しちまうんだもんな
うん なんだ？
Huh? What is it?
MYSTERIOUS WOODS ADVENTURE
あ 土井が行きたがってた
アトラクションか
Oh, it's the ride Doi wanted to try.
ガキくせぇ
これ乗るのに400円だろ？
How childish.
It's 400 yen to get in!
地元でスト２
８回やった方がマシだぜ
I'd much rather play Street Fighter II
eight times back at home.
（鬼）
うははは！
（ガタン）
（女）あーっ！
（バシ）
- うん！
- いて！
Ouch!
う…子供向けかと思ったら
案外怖かったな おい
I thought it was for kiddies,
but it's surprisingly scary...
（大野）
あ！
May as well go since we're here...
そういえばココに来てから
ゲームばっかだったしな
（歩く音）
ぐ…
土井に大口叩いた事が
悔やまれるぜ
Now I'm regretting boasting
about this place to Doi...
（ウィーン）
（大野）う…
大野はしゃいでるな
Ono's really enjoying this.
表にはあまり出さねぇけど
何となく伝わってくるぜ
She doesn't show it
but I can tell, somehow.
（ウィーン）
（春雄）うお！
- う…
- 大野さ
Ono, have your parents ever taken
you to an amusement park before?
親に遊園地とか連れてって
もらった事あんの？
- ううん
- やっぱりな
Didn't think so...
仕方ねぇ
Well, I've got no choice.
I'll have to tend to this poor girl's
wants 'til the very end.
この可哀想な奴のワガママを
最後まで聞いてやるか…
今度はなんだ？
What's next?
（虫の音）
これはさっき…
Isn't this...?
土井とこいつに乗るのが嫌で
Didn't she run away
to the arcade before
ゲームコーナーに
逃げて来たんじゃ…
because she didn't want to ride
this with Doi?
お？
（静かな音楽）
お…
あれ なんで俺
今緊張したの？
Huh? Why am I nervous
all of a sudden?
Sorry, folks.
（職員）
ごめんなさい
今日はもう終わりなんです
We're closed for today.
で なんで俺 ちょっと
ホッとしてるの？
Why am I kind of relieved?
（ぐいっ）
（ブルルン）
結局 閉園まで
遊んじまったな…うっ！
So we ended up hanging out
together until the park closed...
疲れて寝ちまってる
She's so tired that she's nodded off.
ここんとこ
元気なかったからな
She was pretty down before.
こいつも色々耐えてるもんが
あったんだろな…
I'm sure she's had to endure a lot, too...
（キンコンカンコン）
（騒ぐ声）
あぁ とうとう
始まっちまったな
Ah, so it begins.
The second-semester hell.
地獄の２学期…
（女子）
ねぇねぇ 聞いた？
Hey, did you hear?
大野さん親の都合で
海外へ転校するみたい
Ono's parents are
making her go to school abroad!
What, really?
ええ マジキー？
そういえば今日いないね
Actually, she's absent today...
-Is she just moving?
-Her parents getting a divorce?
両親の離婚とか？
- 海外の移住って聞いたよ
- この時期で転校なんて
-She's emigrating, right?
-Moving, at this time!
It's so sad...
超寂しい…
（悲しい音楽）
なんで俺こんなに
ショック受けてるの？
Why am I so affected by this?
HI SCORE GIRL
（鳥のさえずり）
（悲しい音楽）
FAREWELL TO ONO
（先生）
大野さんは今日の夕方
ロスに向け日本を発ちます
This evening
Ono will be leaving Japan
for Los Angeles.
えー
What?
いやいや
前々から言ってたでしょ
Come on, you knew already!
大野さんを温かく
見送ってあげようじゃないか
Let's give her a warm send-off!
（パチパチ）
おおお！
Miss Ono...
大野さん！
（パチパチ）
（カメラの音）
大野さん
可愛い筆記用具を選んだぞ
Ono, I chose a cute pencil case!
Persimmons!
柿…
Please have my mini four-wheel drive!
It's the fastest there is!
僕のミニ四駆で一番
速いヤツだ もらってくれ
（土井）
そんな下郎の
チマチマした物より
Forget about these trivial trinkets.
Take my gift.
- 僕のをもらってくれよ
- ひでぇセンスだ
What terrible taste...
皆それぞれ 大野への
贈り物は渡したか？
Has everyone given
Ono her goodbye presents?
まだ矢口くんが
渡してません！
Yaguchi hasn't given anything yet!
矢口 お前まさか？
Yaguchi? Seriously?
忘れました
I forgot.
（女子）
ひどい 皆プレゼント
買うって決めたのに
So mean! We agreed
we'd all buy something, too!
（男子）
お前には人を送ってやる
思いやりがないのか
Don't you know how important it is
to send someone off nicely?
（先生）
謝罪しろ春雄
オタンコナスめ
Apologize, Haruo! Nitwit!
劣等生である事も
ついでに謝れ！
Whilst you're at it,
apologize for being a slacker!
It makes no sense!
意味分かんねぇよ！
ったく な？
Jeez... You see?
クラスでお前と絡むと
ロクな事にならねぇ
Nothing good ever comes
from mixing with you in class.
行くなら行くで
早く行っちゃえよ
If you're leaving,
then leave quickly!
俺の聖域も
荒らされなくて済むから
Without you trampling
on my sacred territory
せいせいするぜ
I'll be mighty relieved.
- なんてこと言うんだ！
- ぬお！
How can you say that, Haruo?
（男子）
聖域って何の事だよ
"Sacred territory"?
This jerk is just merciless!
残忍極まりない野郎だぜ
最悪 あんな奴
ほっときましょう
Ugh! Let's just be done with him.
（タン）
（歩く音）
（ウィーン）
（先生）
大野
Ono, I'd hoped to see you
to graduation, but...
卒業式で送って
あげたかったが仕方がない
向こうでも元気でな
Well, take care over there.
-Ono!
-Take care!
- 大野さん！
- 元気でね
- 晶(あきら)ちゃーん！
- 大野さーん！
Akira!
体気をつけてねー
Take care of yourself!
達者でな大野さん！
（ブルルン）
またね！
大野さーん！
さよならの追いかけは
5ｍまでって言っただろ！
I told you! Limit your farewell chase
to five meters!
あーあ
貴重な目の保養的存在が
Well, there goes our school's
sight for sore eyes...
- 居なくなっちゃったか
- 私は？
-What about me?
-Our one and only healing flower...
- 唯一の癒しの花が…
- 私！
（歩く音）
別にプレゼント忘れてた
わけじゃねぇんだぜ
It's not like I actually forgot
to get her a present.
あの変わりもんに
何あげりゃいいのか
I just had no idea what to get
見当付かなかっただけだ
for such a weird kid.
（タッ）
（悲しい音楽）
ふん お袋にもらった
あいつ用の千円だが
Mom gave me a thousand yen
to spend on her.
（チャリン）
ゲーセンで使っちまえ
Might as well use it at the arcade!
I mean...
大体なんで俺があいつに
プレゼントしなきゃいけない
Why should I have to get
her a present?
（座る音）
俺の憩いの場を
荒らしに荒らし
She invaded my sacred ground
and caused a scene.
俺のプライドをズタズタに
切り裂いた張本人だ
She's the one who tore my pride to shreds.
最後のライバルが
舞台から降りたおかげで
Now that my ultimate rival has
stepped down from the stage
豪指の春雄伝説が
また始まる
the legend of the godly Haruo
can begin anew!
胸を張って
ゲーセンに通えるんだ
I can return to the arcade
with my head held high!
俺の…俺だけの世界
This... is my world!
元々俺は一人でこうして
遊ぶのが好きなんだ
I've always preferred playing
by myself!
縛られる事も
文句を言われることもねぇ
No ties, no complaints.
ゲームは俺の唯一の取り柄！
Games are my one true strength!
でもあの女が現れて
But that girl appeared...
and I realized that she could surpass me
俺の更に上を行く
手の及ばない存在だと
気付いた時
and go even further...
身を引き裂かれるような
思いだった
and that just killed me!
憎くてウザくて
I hated it, loathed it...
忌々しくて
いけすかねぇ存在だった…
She was so frustrating,
so annoying!
でもなぜかゲーセンに入ると
あいつの姿を探しちまう
But still, when I'd enter an arcade
I'd look for her.
あいつの腕を認めざるを
得なくて尊敬した…
I couldn't help but acknowledge
and respect her skill.
心意気にホレボレした
She had her charm, in a way.
初めて同志ができたと
胸も躍った
Somehow I was happy...
finding my first comrade.
（男性）
春雄 春雄
Haruo... Haruo!
- お前の気持ちはそれだけか
- あ！
Is that all your feelings are about?
（ガイル）
己に正直になれ 春雄
Be honest with yourself, Haruo.
あの子との戦いは
まだ終わっていない
Your battle with that kid isn't over yet.
お前の戦いが
俺の新たなる力となるだろう
This fight of yours...
it will give me new strength!
- ファネッフー！
- う！
Sonic Boom!
うあ…
（ゲーム）
へへへ 春雄さんよ
初めてお目にかかるな
Heh, heh, Haruo!
First time laying eyes on you!
これ以上見栄を張るようなら
後悔することになるぜ
If you keep up this stubborn
stiff upper lip, you'll regret it!
グワーㇵッㇵッㇵッ
うう…
（ゲーム）
今タイムはいくつだ
時間がないぞ
What time is it?
There's no time!
今日の夕方 ロスに向け
日本を発ちます
This evening she'll be leaving Japan
for Los Angeles...
（切ない音楽）
（ゲーム）
行け そして頼朝(よりとも)をうて
Go forth and defeat Yoritomo!
もう くよくよして
いられないわ
Quit holding yourself back!
Rawr, argh argh!
ウォウッ！
何ボヤボヤしてやがんだ
さっさと行きやがれ！
Stop stalling! Go!
（タッ）
（明るい音楽）
Faster...
（ガイル）
早く！　速く！
Quick, hurry!
（ガイル）迅く！
（春雄）大野ー！
Ono!
（走る音）
（飛行機の音）
（じいや）
お嬢様
お供できなくて残念です
Oh, young Miss, it's such a shame
I can't accompany you!
じいやは
パチンコ中毒ゆえ
As a pachinko addict, I have no choice
but to remain in Japan.
日本にとどまらざるを
得ないのです
ロスでもお元気で お嬢様
Do take care of yourself
over in Los Angeles.
向こうで
ケンカを売られたら
If you get into a scrap over there,
jab them right in the median line!
一本拳で正中線を
こづいてやりなさい
（ウィーン）
（走る音）
（春雄）ふーふー
（大野）あ！
ふーふーふー
あ あのな 大野
Hey, Ono!
今度ＳＮＫからな
I heard that SNK are going to release
a game called Fatal Fury soon...
「餓狼伝説(がろうでんせつ)」って
格闘ゲームが出るんだよ
スト２が
あんなに流行ったから
With Street Fighter II being so popular,
I knew they'd make more fighting games!
また格闘ゲームが
出てくると思ってたんだ
俺の予想だと
I reckon this'll fire up the arcades
even more!
これからゲーセンが
盛り上がってくるぜ
俺達が想像も
つかないような物が
I'm sure they'll keep on releasing stuff
we can't even imagine!
どんどん出てくると思うんだ
こんな時に海外に行くなんて
残念すぎるぜ
Leaving the country at such a time...
It's just such a shame!
To think, such a strong rival
leaving now...
俺も張り合いが持てる奴が
いなくなるのかと思うと
寂しくてしょーがねぇ
It makes me so sad.
（静かな音楽）
お前へ何か贈り物をって
お袋から千円もらったんだ
My mom gave me a load of cash
to get you a present.
でもここへ来る時
電車賃で使っちまった
But I ended up using it
to get the train here.
帰りも考えると結局
お前には何も買えねぇ…
Then with the return journey, too...
I can't buy you anything.
This here
これな お前と
一緒に行ったゲーセン
is from that arcade we went to,
far away.
がしゃどくろの
クレーンゲームで取ったんだ
I got it in the crane game.
母の日にでもお袋にやろうと
財布に忍ばせてあったんだよ
I hid it in my wallet then
thinking I'd give it to my mom
on Mother's Day.
これ この世の物じゃ
ないかも知れないし
This thing might be
kind of otherworldly
色々な意味で
気色悪いかも知れねぇけど
and it might be creepy
in so many ways...
今 お前にあげれる物は
これしかねぇ
but this is all I have
to give you right now!
もらってくれるか？
Will you take it?
（効果音）
大野？
Ono...
（ウィーン）
（大野）
う…う…
（母）
晶 そろそろ行くわよ
Akira!
We're leaving!
うう…
うあああああ！
（大きく泣く声）
（姉）
ちょっ 何やってんの？
What are you doing?
- 飛行機に乗り遅れちゃうよ
- うあああ！
We'll miss our flight!
（タッ）
（春雄）あだだだ！
Ouch! Ouch!
（姉）
晶 もうこの子ってば
Akira, what are you doing?
（大野）
ああああ！
（起きる音）
ははっ
（飛行機の音）
投げハメに頼らないくらい
ガイルを強化しねぇとな
Guess I'll have to work
on my Guile skills
so I don't have to rely
on Throw Jank...
次会った時
互角に戦えるように…
So when we meet next time,
we can fight on equal ground.
Subtitle translation by
Helen O'Horan
（春雄）
駄菓子屋とか酒屋とかの
店頭にあるゲーム筐体って
The cabinets at the front of
candy shops and liquor stores...
I love how they're so cheap to play!
料金が安いの多くて
嬉しいよな
一回20円とか
10円とかまであってさ
Sometimes as little as
ten or 20 yen per play!
まあ メンテの悪い
とこも多いし
Still, they're not often well-maintained
二人プレイしてたりすると
狭くて困んだよなー
and multiplayer games can get
a little cramped...
"日本語字幕 パク・スミン"